{
    "subject": "Nora_Hanen",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Bo_Buchanan",
    "human_readable": "Nora Hanen is married to Bo Buchanan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9142983555793762,
            "question": "What is Nora Hanen's relationship to Bo Buchanan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9032472372055054,
            "question": "Name someone who is married to Bo Buchanan."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9018916487693787,
            "question": "To whom is Nora Hanen married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8951817154884338,
            "question": "Is Nora Hanen married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8608209490776062,
            "question": "Who is married to Bo Buchanan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8500412106513977,
            "question": "Is Bo Buchanan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8347538709640503,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Nora Hanen and Bo Buchanan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.693949818611145,
            "question": "Who is Nora Hanen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31496572494506836,
            "question": "Name a person who is married."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1370047777891159,
            "question": "Who are the two people involved in a marriage relationship mentioned here?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nora Hanen is married to Bo Buchanan.",
            "html": "yago_12017_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a person who is married.",
            "html": "yago_12017_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Nora Hanen?",
            "html": "yago_12017_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about the relationship between Nora Hanen and Bo Buchanan?",
            "html": "yago_12017_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12017_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12017_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12017_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12017_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12017_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12017_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12017_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12017_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12017_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12017_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents mention that Nora Hanen moved to Llanview in 1992 and met her future husband, Bo Buchanan (document #20), became engaged to him in 1993 (document #45), and later married him again (document #32)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Nora Hanen and Bo Buchanan were initially engaged, but they did not get married. They postponed their marriage due to Nora's brain tumor surgery. The information provided does not support the statement that Nora Hanen is currently married to Bo Buchanan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}